A Guide to the Papers of the President of the University of Virginia, Office Administrative Files, 1987-2003(2002-2003)
Special Collections, University of Virginia Library
- Series III: Restricted Files
  - Gifts & Grants "Me-My", pulled from general files, 2002 - 2003 (Box-folder 39:1)
  - Gifts & Grants "N-O", pulled from general files, 2002 - 2003 (Box-folder 39:2)
  - Gifts & Grants "P", pulled from general files, 2002 - 2003 (Box-folder 39:3)
  - Gifts & Grants "Q-R", pulled from general files, 2002 - 2003 (Box-folder 39:4)
  - Gifts & Grants "Sa-Se", pulled from general files, 2002 - 2003 (Box-folder 39:5)
  - Gifts & Grants "Sh-Sm", pulled from general files, 2002 - 2003 (Box-folder 39:6)
  - Gifts & Grants "Sn-Sy", pulled from general files, 2002 - 2003 (Box-folder 40:1)
  - Gifts & Grants "T-U", pulled from general files, 2002 - 2003 (Box-folder 40:2)
  - Gifts & Grants "V-Wh", pulled from general files, 2002 - 2003 (Box-folder 40:3)
  - Gifts & Grants "Wi-Z", pulled from general files, 2002 - 2003 (Box-folder 40:4)
  - "I" Miscellaneous Restricted Files, pulled from general files, 2002 - 2003 (Box-folder 40:5)
  - "J-M" Miscellaneous Restricted Files, pulled from general files, 2002 - 2003 (Box-folder 40:6)
  - "P-R" Miscellaneous Restricted Files, pulled from general files, 2002 - 2003 (Box-folder 40:7)
  - Recommendations "A-T", pulled from general files, 2002 - 2003 (Box-folder 40:8)
  - Research & Graduate Studies - Search for Vice-President, pulled from general files, 2003 (Box-folder 40:9)
  - "S-V" Miscellaneous Restricted Files, pulled from general files, 2002 - 2003 (Box-folder 41:1)
  - Seldom Used Permanent Files - Miscellaneous Restricted Files, pulled from seldom used permanent files, 1995 - 2002 (Box-folder 41:2)
  - University Police, pulled from general files, 2002 July (Box-folder 41:3)
  - University of Virginia Investment Management Company, pulled from general files, 2003 April- July (Box-folder 41:4)
  - University of Virginia Investment Management Company, pulled from general files, 2003 January - March (Box-folder 41:5)
  - University of Virginia Investment Management Company, pulled from general files, 2002 October- December (Box-folder 41:6)
  - University of Virginia Investment Management Company, pulled from general files, 2002 September (Box-folder 41:7)
  - University of Virginia Investment Management Company, pulled from general files, 2002 July - August (Box-folder 41:8)